let MCQS = [{
    question: "JWST stands for ?",
    choice1: "james Webb Space Telescope",
    choice2: "John Webb Space Telescope",
    choice3: "Jim Webb Space Telescope",
    choice4: "None",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "JWST is launched on ?",
    choice1: "20th December 2021",
    choice2: "20th November 2021",
    choice3: "25th December 2021",
    choice4: "25th November 2021",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "Where JWST is placed in space?",
    choice1: "Lagrange 1",
    choice2: "Lagrange 2 ",
    choice3: "Lagrange 3",
    choice4: "Lagrange 4",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "How many mirrors are used in JWST ?",
    choice1: "18",
    choice2: "16",
    choice3: "14",
    choice4: "12",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What is the shape of mirrors ?",
    choice1: "Square",
    choice2: "Circle",
    choice3: "Pentagon",
    choice4: "Hexagon",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: " Which sensors are used in capturing images ?",
    choice1: "Guidance Sensor",
    choice2: "Near Infrared Imager and Slitless Spectrograph",
    choice3: "UV sensor",
    choice4: "None",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "How many layers of sunshield are used to protect the mirrors?",
    choice1: "3",
    choice2: "4",
    choice3: "5",
    choice4: "6",
    answer: 2
},{
               question: " What is the telescope’s primary mirror material?",
    choice1: "Beryllium coated with Gold",
    choice2: " Aluminum",
    choice3: "Metal",
    choice4: "Iron",
    answer: 0
},
            {
               question: "What types of light spectrum JWST can detect?",
    choice1: "Visible light",
    choice2: "IR rays",
    choice3: " Microwaves",
    choice4: "UV rays",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "10. What is the mirror diameter of JWST?",
    choice1: "6.9m",
    choice2: "7.9m",
    choice3: "6,3m",
    choice4: "6.5m",
    answer: 3
}];